Guide to the Terry Sanford Papers, 1926-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Legislative Files Series, 1986-1992
  - Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs Subseries, 1986-1992
    - Subcommittee on International Finance and Monetary Policy, 1986-1992
      - Cigarette Exports, 1989-1990 (Box 68)
      - Coast Guard User Fee, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Charlotte: Business, 1992 (Box 68)
      - Condition of Bank Insurance Fund, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Correspondence, letters, opinions, 1990-1992 (Box 68)
      - Cotton, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Cove Bank, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Cyanamid-Duty Suspension, 1990-1992 (Box 68)
      - Deposit Insurance Reform, 1990, undated (Box 68)
      - Duty Suspension:
        - BIT, 1992 (Box 68)
        - Tamoxifen, 1992 (Box 68)
      - Early Bank Closure, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Enterprise for the Americas, 1990 (Box 68)
      - Environment, 1991-1992 (Box 68)
      - Export control, 1987, (3 folders) (Box 68)
      - Foreign Corrupt Practices Act, 1987 (Box 68)
      - Foreign Exchange, 1988 (Box 68)
      - Foreign Investment, 1988 (Box 68)
      - Foreign Trade Zones, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Garn Superfund Liability Bill, 1990 (Box 68)
      - GATT: (General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade):
        - Eastern Europe, 1989-1992 (Box 68)
        - EC (European Community) oilseed, TS-Sig NATOry, 1991 (Box 68)
        - Soda Ash, 1991-1992 (Box 68)
        - Statements on trade, 1987-1992 (Box 68)
        - Talks, agriculture, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Hoechst Celanese Corporation, 1987 (Box 68)
      - Import stats, 1987 (Box 69)
      - George M., 1992 (Box 69)
      - International debit, 1987 (Box 69)
      - International Economic Policy Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 69)
      - International Securities Enforcement Act, 1988 (Box 69)
      - Japan, 1991-1992 (Box 69)
      - KABI Pharmaceuticals, 1992 (Box 69)
      - Lackawanna, 1992 (Box 69)
      - Lackawanna leather, 1992 (Box 69)
      - Latin American debt, 1988-1990 (Box 69)
      - Less Developed Countries Debt, 1986-1989, (2 folders) (Box 69)
      - Less Developed Countries Debt Hearing, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Leverage Buyout Takeover Amendment, 1987 (Box 69)
      - Lobby letters, 1987 (Box 69)
      - Log Export Bill, 1989 (Box 69)
      - Lumber, 1992 (Box 69)
      - Luxury tax on jewelry, 1991 (Box 69)
      - Meat Trade issues, 1989 (Box 69)
      - Memo:
        - Garn Bill (Superfund Bill), 1990 (Box 69)
        - Lender Liability, 1990 (Box 69)
        - Mexico Free Trade: Fast Track, 1991 (Box 69)
      - Mixed credits, 1989 (Box 69)
      - Monetary Policy Hearing, 1990, Feb.14 (Box 69)
      - Mortgage discrimination, 1990, May16 (Box 69)
      - Multilateral Development Banks, 1987-1991 (Box 69)
      - Multilateral Export Control Sanctions Act, 1987 (Box 69)
      - Multilateral Investment Guaranty Authority, 1987 (Box 69)
      - International Finance and Monetary Policy; NAFTA (National American Free Trade Agreement, 1991-1992 (Box 69)
      - NAFTA background, undated, (2 folders) (Box 69)
      - NAFTA conference, 1991-1992 (Box 69)
      - NAFTA, Fast Track, 1991-1992 (Box 70)
      - Nags Head Woods, 1990-1991 (Box 70)
      - Norton takeover, 1990,Apr. 19 (Box 70)
      - Nuzum/ Crawford: Nominations, 1991 (Box 70)
      - Overseas Private Investment Corporation, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 70)
      - Paine Webber, Remarks Housing Tapes, 1990 (Box 70)
      - Peanuts, 1991 (Box 70)
      - Pork, 1991 (Box 70)
      - Pre-shipment inspection, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 70)
      - S.625, 1992 (Box 70)
      - S. 696, Bank Efficiency Act, Press Release statement, 1991 (Box 70)
      - Semiconductor Trade Issues, 1987-1989 (Box 70)
      - Semiconductors, 1991 (Box 70)
      - Semiconductor Trade Agreement: U.S.-Japan, 1991 (Box 70)
      - SEC/CFTC Jurisdiction, 1990, Mar.3 (Box 70)
      - Small Business: Exporting, 1988 (Box 70)
      - Sonoco Fibre Drums, 1992 (Box 70)
      - Steel, 1992 (Box 70)
      - Steel Industry, 1987-1988 (Box 70)
      - Statement: Hearing on S.2827 and Environmental Risks to Lenders, 1990 (Box 70)
      - Sweater case: Hong Kong, Korea, Taiwan, 1990 (Box 70)
      - Symms Amendment, Multilateral Development Banks, 1988 (Box 70)
      - Testimony of Steven A. Seelig, 1990, July19 (Box 70)
      - Textiles, 1992 (Box 70)
      - Tiwan-GATT, 1990-1992 (Box 70)
      - Tied Aid, 1989 (Box 70)
      - Third World Economic Development, 1987 (Box 70)
      - Tobacco Trade, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 70)
      - Trade:
        - 1987-1990 (Box 70)
        - Bills, 1987 (Box 70)
        - Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 70)
        - Finance, 1989 (Box 70)
        - Policy, 1989 (Box 70)
        - Smokeless Tobacco, 1987-1989 (Box 70)
        - Japan, 1990 (Box 70)
      - Trade: Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 71)
      - U.S.-Canada Softwood Lumber, 1991 (Box 71)
      - U.S.-Japanese Trade, 1992 (Box 71)
      - Westinghouse, Aid, 1992 (Box 71)
      - World Bank GCI, 1988 (Box 71)
      - World Bank Poverty, 1987-1988 (Box 71)
      - Written statement: Lender Liability for Environmental Claims Before the Committee, 1990 (Box 71)
    - Subcommittee on Securities, 1985-1992
      Specifically deals with finance issues. Subjects consist of the federal reserve system and the savings and loans industry.
      - Anti-greenmail, 1987 (Box 71)
      - Amendments for the Banking Bill, 1991 (Box 71)
      - Bank Efficiency Act, 1991 (Box 71)
      - Bank Insurance Fund, 1991 (Box 71)
      - Bank Insurance Fund Recap., 1991 (Box 71)
      - Bank of New England, 1991 (Box 71)
      - Banking Bill:
        - S-790, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 71)
        - Amendments:
          - 1987 (Box 71)
          - Credit Enhance, 1992 (Box 71)
        - FDICIA, 1991 (Box 71)
        - Markup S.543, 1991, (3 folders) (Box 71)
      - Banking Budget Reconciliation, 1987 (Box 71)
      - Banking Insurance Fund Hearing, 1990 (Box 71)
      - Banking Insurance Reform, 1991-1992 (Box 71)
      - Banks: Staff memorandum, 1988-1989 (Box 71)
      - BIF Fund, 1990, Sept.11-12, (2 folders) (Box 71)
      - Brokered Deposits, 1991 (Box 71)
      - Burlington Takeover, 1987-1988 (Box 71)
      - Cannon Mills Pensions, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 71)
      - Capital Intusion, 1991 (Box 71)
      - Central America Bill, 1990, Sept.13 (Box 71)
      - Check Hold, 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 71)
      - Clark nomination, 1991 (Box 71)
      - Colass- Steagall Analysis, 1991 (Box 72)
      - Committee markup of legislation, Vol, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 72)
      - Commodity Futures Trading Commission/SEC, 1990 (Box 72)
      - CFTC/SEC: Securities Industry Association, 1990, Mar.19 (Box 72)
      - Common Bond/Credit Unions, 1991 (Box 72)
      - Community Reinvestment Act, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 72)
      - Comprehensive Deposit Insurance Reform, 1991 (Box 72)
      - Corporate Financing Week Interview, 1990,Apr. 18-Sept. 19 (Box 72)
      - Corporate Takeover Bill, 1987 (Box 72)
      - Corporate Takeover letters, 1987-1989 (Box 72)
      - Credit Card Cap., 1991 (Box 72)
      - Credit Card Disclosure/Mint/markup (Box 72)
      - Credit Card Legislation, 1988, (3 folders) (Box 72)
      - Credit Reform: Fair Credit Reporting, 1987 (Box 72)
      - Credit Union, 1987-1991, (2 folders) (Box 72)
      - Cross Guarantee, 1991 (Box 72)
      - Dear Colleague, 1990,Apr. 18 (Box 72)
      - Deposit Insurance Reform 1990, (3 folders) (Box 72)
      - Director interlocks, 1988 (Box 72)
      - Directors and Officers Liability, 1991 (Box 72)
      - Discount Window, 1991 (Box 72)
      - Edgar, 1988 (Box 72)
      - Electronic Fund Transfer, 1987 (Box 72)
      - Emergency Bank Investment Fund, 1991, (3 folders) (Box 72)
      - Emergency Bank Investment Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 73)
      - Emergency Bank Investment Fund Act: Early Resolution andnum;310, 1991 (Box 73)
      - Emergency Bank Investment Corp.: Early Resolutions, 1991-1992 (Box 73)
      - Exchange Controls, 1987-1988 (Box 73)
      - Exit Fees, 1987 (Box 73)
      - Export-Import Bank Bill, 1987-1991 (Box 73)
      - Failing thrifts, 1988 (Box 73)
      - Fast Track S.109, 1991-1992 (Box 73)
      - FDIC, 1984-1988 (Box 73)
      - Federal Reserve:
        - Background, 1988-1991 (Box 73)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 73)
        - Regulations, 1988 (Box 73)
      - Federal Savings and Loan Insurance Corporation Resolution Commission: National Commission of Thrift Industry, 1988 (Box 73)
      - FHLBB/FSLIC (Federal Home Loan Bank Board/Federal Savings and Loan Insurance Corporation), 1986-1988 (Box 73)
      - FHLBB individual cases, 1988 (Box 73)
      - Financial Institutions Reform: Recovery and Enforcement Act: Background, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 73)
      - Firewalls, 1991 (Box 73)
      - First options, 1987 (Box 73)
      - First Quarter Profitability of Private Sector Thrifts, 1990, July25 (Box 73)
      - Forbearance, 1987 (Box 73)
      - Foreign Bank issues, 1991 (Box 73)
      - FSLIC:
        - Brokered Deposits, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Capital Standards, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 73)
        - Credit Union, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Deferred Loan Losses, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Federal Home Loan Banks, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Financing costs, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Goodwill, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Markup amendments, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Memos, 1988-1989 (Box 73)
        - Moratorium, 1988 (Box 73)
        - North Carolina savings and loans, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Open statements, 1989 (Box 74)
        - Premiums, 1989 (Box 74)
        - State Powers, 1989 (Box 74)
        - Suggested amendments, 1989 (Box 74)
        - Takeovers, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 74)
      - General memos: Overview, 1991 (Box 74)
      - Globalization of Capital Markets Hearing, 1987 (Box 74)
      - Globalization of Securities Market, 1989 (Box 74)
      - Government checks, Lifeline, 1988 (Box 74)
      - Grants, 1989 (Box 74)
      - Home Equity Loans, 1986-1989 (Box 74)
      - Hostile bank takeovers, 1988 (Box 74)
      - Insider trading, 1987-1988 (Box 74)
      - Insurance, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 74)
      - Insurance issues, 1987-1989 (Box 74)
      - Intellectual property rights, 1990 (Box 74)
      - International capital markets, 1987 (Box 74)
      - Interstate, 1991 (Box 74)
      - Interstate banking, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 74)
      - Interviews with Lauren Martin, 1990, Aug.7 (Box 74)
      - J.P. Stevens takeover, 1988 (Box 74)
      - Junk bonds, 1986-1990 (Box 74)
      - Kannapolis, N.C.: Cannon Mills Pension, 1991 (Box 74)
      - Lender liability, 1990-1991 (Box 74)
      - Lender Liability Under the Superfund Law: Banking Committee, 1990, July19 (Box 74)
      - Lincoln Asset Management Co., 1988 (Box 74)
      - Manager's Amendments: Bank Insurance Fund, 1991 (Box 74)
      - Market crash, 1988-1989 (Box 74)
      - McKinney Act, 1988 (Box 74)
      - Merchants National Corporation, 1989-1990 (Box 74)
      - Minimum wage data, 1988 (Box 74)
      - Monetary policy, 1989 (Box 74)
      - Money laundering: (Box 75)
        - 1985-1990, (2 folders) (Box 75)
        - Markup, 1991 (Box 75)
      - Mortgage coinsurance, undated (Box 75)
      - Mortgage-backed securities, 1986-1989 (Box 75)
      - Mortgage bankers, 1992 (Box 75)
      - Mortgage discrimination, 1988-1989 (Box 75)
      - Multilateral Development Banks and Environment, 1988, Feb.15-Oct. 4 (Box 75)
      - New York luncheon: stock market crash, 1988 (Box 75)
      - Nominations for FDIC, 1992-1993 (Box 75)
      - Non-market Economics Law, 1984-1987 (Box 75)
      - Opening: Talking points, 1988 (Box 75)
      - Outline of Research Relating to the Thrift Crisis, 1990, June20 (Box 75)
      - Pension funds 1989-1990 (Box 75)
      - Possible Introduction of Senate Bill on Prosecution of SandL Crooks, 1990, June13 (Box 75)
      - Preemption: CTS, 1987 (Box 75)
      - Proxmire Bill, 1987 (Box 75)
      - Proxy system, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 75)
      - Public Utility Holding Company Act, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 75)
      - Purchased Mortgage Servicing Rights, 1991 (Box 75)
      - Qualified Thrift Lender Test, 1991 (Box 75)
      - Resolution Trust Corporation Fund, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 75)
      - Resolution Trust Corporation: Non Profits: Thad Woodard, 1989-1990 (Box 76)
      - RICO (Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act), 1990, May24-June 29 (Box 76)
      - RTC ( Resolution Trust Corporation) Vulture Fund, ca. 1990-1991 (Box 76)
      - Ryan, Tim: Nomination, 1990, Mar.20-Apr. 15 (Box 76)
      - S.824: Emergency Bank Investment Fund Act, 1991 (Box 76)
      - Salmon Brothers hearings, 1991 (Box 76)
      - Sanford Amendments Nos. 297-311, 1991 (Box 76)
      - Sanford's signed letters, 1990,Apr. 27-Oct. 19 (Box 76)
      - Savings and Loans (SandL):
        - 1990 (Box 76)
        - All dear colleagues and SandL, 1990, May17-June 14 (Box 76)
        - All memo to Jennifer Hillman, 1990 July25-Aug. 2 (Box 76)
        - Brief summary of S.2735, ca. 1990-1991 (Box 76)
        - Congressional records, 1990, Feb.23-June 26 (Box 76)
        - Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 76)
        - Crimes, 1990, June7-Sept. 14 (Box 76)
        - Crisis, 1990, Aug.1-13 (Box 76)
        - Deals, 1988-1990,July 16, (2 folders) (Box 76)
        - Department of Justice: Statements and Fact sheet, 1990, July (Box 76)
        - Director and officers liability, 1990, Sept.3 (Box 76)
        - Export Administration Act, 1990, Oct.3 (Box 76)
        - FDIC premiums, 1990, Sept.13-26 (Box 76)
        - Financial Service Reform: Glass Steagall Act: Should Bankers Be Brokers?, 1990, Mar. 30-June 19 (Box 76)
        - Floor statement: Support for the Wirth/Graham/Dixon Bill on SandL Crooks, 1990, June11 (Box 76)
        - Foreign Deposit, 1990, Oct.5 (Box 76)
        - Fraud, 1990, June25-Sept. 7 (Box 76)
        - Fraud information, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 76)
        - Fraud, Vol. I and II, 1990, (5 folders) (Box 76)
        - Modernizing Financial Services Industry, 1990,Apr. 3-24 (Box 76)
        - News clippings and other articles 1990, May21-22 (Box 76)
        - News: Office of Thrift Supervision: OTS Seeks anddollar;40.9 Million Restitution From Keating and Five ACC Directors, 1990, Aug. 9 (Box 76)
        - New release: Sanford/ Sasser Propose Measure to reform Takeover Laws, 1990, Feb. 22 (Box 76)
        - N.C. banks, 1990, Sept. 4 (Box 76)
        - N.C. Deserves It's Fair Share of Federal Fund, 1990, June21 (Box 76)
        - N.C. Savings and Loans, 1990 (Box 76)
        - Pickens/ Koito, 1990, Sept.28-Oct. 2 (Box 76)
        - Regulations, 1987-1992, (2 folders) (Box 76)
        - Research, 1981-1990, (2 folders) (Box 76)
        - SandL financial condition, 1990, Aug.30 (Box 76)
        - Speeches, 1987 (Box 76)
        - Topics for floor statements, 1990 (Box 76)
      - Securities, 1991 (Box 77)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)
        - Authorization, 1987-1991 (Box 77)
        - Regulations, 1987 (Box 77)
        - Securities Exchange Bill, 1988 (Box 77)
        - Sweep the Street proposed regulations, 1987 (Box 77)
      - Securities Investor Protection Act coverage, 1991 (Box 77)
      - Self Help Credit Union, 1987-1990 (Box 77)
      - Short Selling: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 77)
      - Signature Guarantee, 1988 (Box 77)
      - Southwest Plan Deals, 1988-1990 (Box 77)
      - State Banking Powers, 1990-1991 (Box 77)
      - Statement Takeover Reform Bill, 1989, Nov.20-1990 (Box 77)
      - Statement of the American Banks Association on Lender Liability Act of 1990, 1990, July 19 (Box 77)
      - Study of Corporate Takeovers, 1987 (Box 77)
      - Takeover:
        - Background reports, 1987 (Box 77)
        - Markup, 1987-1988, (5 folders) (Box 77)
      - Tax and Higher Ed issues, 1986-1987 (Box 77)
      - Thrift Bank merger, 1985-1987 (Box 77)
      - Thrift Enhancement Markup, 1988, May25-July 25 (Box 77)
      - Treasury news, 1990, Aug.8 (Box 77)
      - Unified National Ban, 1987 (Box 77)
      - Urban Aid, 1991-1992 (Box 77)
      - USG/Merrill Lynch, 1990, May25-27 (Box 77)
      - Wirth- Graham Bill, 1987 (Box 77)
    - Housing and Urban Affairs, 1986-1992
      Primarily consists of housing legislation. Subjects include community development, federal housing, rural development, and rural housing. Urban issues addressed include mass transit, renewal, and revitalization programs.
      - Affordable Housing Act., 1991, (3 folders) (Box 78)
      - Assisted Housing, 1992 (Box 78)
      - Budget, 1990-1992 (Box 78)
      - Budget Committee, 1990 (Box 78)
      - Cash Management Improvement Act, 1992 (Box 78)
      - Commission on Regulatory Barriers Report, 1990-1992 (Box 78)
      - Community Development Block grants, 1986-1990 (Box 78)
      - Community Investment Corporation of North Carolina, 1991-1992 (Box 78)
      - Community Reinvestment Act, 1988-1991, (4 folders) (Box 78)
      - Cranston- D'Amato Bill:
        - Home Formula, 1991 (Box 78)
        - National Affordable Housing Act, 1989-1990 (Box 78)
      - Drugs, 1989-1990 (Box 78)
      - Education: African-American men, 1990 (Box 78)
      - Enterprise Zones, 19891992, (4 folders) (Box 78)
      - Fair Housing, 1986-1990 (Box 78)
      - Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 78)
      - Federal Housing Administration:
        - Multifamily finances, 1992 (Box 78)
        - Reform, 1989-1992, (4 folders) (Box 78)
      - Federal Housing Enterprises Regulatory Reform Act, 1992 (Box 78)
      - Federal Housing Finance Board, 1991-1992 (Box 78)
      - Government-sponsored legislation, 1992 (Box 79)
      - Greensboro's Affordable House Initiative, 1992 (Box 79)
      - Greensboro Housing Hearing, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - Highway Bill, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - Historic preservation, 1987 (Box 79)
      - Hone/CDBG, 1992 (Box 79)
      - Housing and Community Development Act of 1987 (Box 79)
      - H.R. 11 (Urban and Package): Established Tax Enterprise Zones, 1992 (Box 79)
      - H.R. 1180: Housing Bill, 1989 (Box 79)
      - HUD: (Box 80)
        - Reform 1992, (2 folders) (Box 80)
        - Scandals, 1989-1991 (Box 80)
      - Jacksonville: Caring Community Committee, 1992 (Box 80)
      - Jack Kemp, 1989-1991 (Box 80)
      - Kemp proposals: HOPE, 1989-1991 (Box 80)
      - Legislation, 1987-1989 (Box 80)
      - Low-income housing crisis, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 80)
      - Low-income tax credit, 1989-1991 (Box 80)
      - Manufactured housing, 1987-1991, (3 folders) (Box 80)
      - Mass Transit Act, 1991 (Box 80)
      - Mass Transit: Bus testing issue, 1991 (Box 80)
      - Migrant Housing Law, 1988 (Box 80)
      - Mixed housing, 1992 (Box 80)
      - National Assisted Housing Management, 1992 (Box 80)
      - National Affordable Housing Act, 1991 (Box 80)
      - National Community Economic Partnership Act, 1991-1992 (Box 80)
      - North Carolina Housing Finance Agency, 1983-1991, (2 folders) (Box 80)
      - N.C. Housing Policy report, 1988, June (Box 81)
      - N.C. Housing Resources, 1985-1990 (Box 81)
      - Northeastern North Carolina Rural Poverty Project, 1989-1991, (3 folders) (Box 81)
      - Policy, 1987-1992, (2 folders) (Box 81)
      - Public Housing, 1987-1991, (2 folders) (Box 81)
      - Public Housing Authority, 1991-1992 (Box 81)
      - Real Estate Procedures Act, 1988-1990 (Box 81)
      - Reauthorization:
        - General issues, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 81)
        - Miscellaneous issues, 1991-1992 (Box 81)
        - Public Housing issues, 1992 (Box 81)
      - Rural development:
        - 1987-1991, (5 folders) (Box 81)
        - Credit issues, 1987-1988 (Box 81)
        - Credit issues, 1987-1991, (2 folders) (Box 82)
        - Leahy Rural Jobs Bill, 1992 (Box 82)
        - North Carolina, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 82)
        - Southern reports, 1986-1988 (Box 82)
        - Statements, 1989 (Box 82)
      - Rural hearing, 1989 (Box 82)
      - Rural housing, 1990, (2 folders)
        - Budget, 1988-1991 (Box 82)
        - Cranston Bill, 1987-1992, (2 folders) (Box 82)
        - Farm credit, 1989-1991 (Box 82)
        - FmHA-GAO, 1991 (Box 82)
        - Guaranteed loan, 1989-1990 (Box 82)
        - Mortgage credit, 1989-1990 (Box 82)
        - Non-profits, 1990 (Box 82)
        - 515 Fraud, 1992 (Box 82)
      - Rural:
        - Prepayment, 1987-1989 (Box 82)
        - Press, 1991-1992 (Box 82)
        - Rental housing, 1992 (Box 82)
        - Reports, 1987-1991, (3 folders) (Box 82)
        - S.825 Housing and Community Development Act of 1987, 1989 (Box 82)
        - S.825 Housing and Community Development Act of 1987, 1989 (Box 83)
        - Sanford Bill, 1989-1990 (Box 83)
      - Secondary Mortgage Market, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 83)
      - Senate: Hearing on Housing Policy, 1992 (Box 83)
      - S.566 Public Housing Block Grant, 1990 (Box 83)
      - Set a Good Example: Hillside, 1992 (Box 83)
      - Special needs, 1989-1992 (Box 83)
      - Studies on affordability, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 83)
      - Urban Mass Transit:
        - 1991 (Box 83)
        - Administration:
          - Light Rail proposals, 1990-1991 (Box 83)
          - Rural issues, 1988-1991 (Box 83)
        - Bus testing issue, 1991 (Box 83)
        - N.C. Numbers, Equity, Issues: DOT requests, 1987-1991 (Box 83)
        - National Transportation Safety Board, 1988 (Box 83)
        - North Carolina, 1989-1992 (Box 83)
        - Reauthorization Transit Symposium, 1991 (Box 83)
        - S.1194, 1991 (Box 83)
      - Urban mass Transit Act, 1991 (Box 83)
      - Urban renewal, 1992 (Box 83)
      - Urban Revitalization, 1992 (Box 83)
  - Foreign Relations Subseries, 1986-1992
    Foreign Relation Subseries is divided into the following sections: General Files; Nominations; International Commission for Central America Recovery and Development; Subcommittee on Near Eastern and South Asian Affairs; Subcommittee on African Affairs; and Defense.
    - General Files, 1987-1992
      Computer generated files containing information on the Soviet Union, the Commonwealth of Independent States, the Persian Gulf War, the INF treaty, and the North American Free Trade Agreement. Types of documents include committee and staff memoranda, reports, legislation, clippings, and Sanford's policy statements.
      - Antarctica, 1989-1990 (Box 84)
      - Aronson, Bernard, 1989 (Box 84)
      - Berlin, 1991 (Box 84)
      - China, 1989 (Box 84)
      - Committee memoranda, 1987-1988, (4 folders) (Box 84)
      - Committee notices, 1987 (Box 84)
      - CIS (Commonwealth of Independent States):
        - S.2532 1992, (3 folders) (Box 84)
        - Aid package, 1992 (Box 84)
        - S.2532 amendments, 1992 (Box 84)
        - Hearing on Legislation Authorizing Assistance, 1992 (Box 84)
        - Terry Sanford statements and press, 1992 (Box 84)
        - Soviet Union: Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 84)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1991, (2 folders) (Box 84)
      - Council of Lebanese American Organizations, 1991-1992 (Box 84)
      - Drug Subcommittee Hearings, 1988 (Box 84)
      - Drugs, 1989 (Box 84)
      - Duke-in- Berlin, 1991 (Box 84)
      - Foreign Assistance Legislation: Markup, 1987 (Box 84)
      - India/ Pakistan Trip proposal, 1989-1990 (Box 84)
      - INF Treaty, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 84)
      - Kuwaiti Ambassador: Coffee opening statement, 1991 (Box 84)
      - Kuwaiti families, 1991 (Box 84)
      - List of countries covered by each subcommittee, 1988 (Box 84)
      - New World Order, 1990 (Box 84)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement, 1992 (Box 85)
      - Overseas travel, 1987-1991 (Box 85)
      - Panama Talking Points, undated (Box 85)
      - Persian Gulf War:
        - 1990-1991, (3 folders) (Box 85)
        - Dear Colleagues, etc., 1990 (Box 85)
        - April Glaspie, 1990-1991 (Box 85)